;

                Privacy Policy                       

≡ [](https://www.krogerwireless.com/)

**Kroger Wireless Privacy Policy**
==================================

At i-wireless LLC, DBA Kroger Wireless (“Kroger Wireless,” or “we,” “us,” “our”) we understand that privacy is important, and we are strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and visitors to our website at [www.krogerwireless.com](http://www.krogerwireless.com/) (collectively, “our website”).

The following information is designed to help you better understand the information that we gather, how we handle the information once we gather it, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct the information we gather. Please note that this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applies to only our products, services, and websites (collectively, “Services”), and not to other companies’ or organizations’ services or websites to which we may link even if they market our products or use the Kroger Wireless name. By visiting our websites or using our Services, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

NOTE: Some of our services may involve features or practices not common to our other websites or services. You should carefully read this entire policy to understand the provisions applicable to our websites and services you are using.

**What information do we collect?**
-----------------------------------

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient and customized experience. This allows us to provide features that are most likely to meet your needs and to customize our service to make your experience easier and more pleasant.

### **Aggregate Data**

Personal Information does not include information that is not used to identify you, such as aggregate or anonymous information. We gather certain usage information like the number and frequency of visitors to our websites. This information may include which URL you just came from, which URL you next visit, what browser you are using, and your IP address. We use such data only in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of our websites, and conduct internal research on our customers’ demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve you. 

This type of aggregated, non-personally identifiable information may also be collected and/or used by third parties that support our services. In addition, we aggregate data and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes.

### **Personally Identifiable Information**

Users are asked to provide certain information when they sign up for our Services such as name, address, phone number, birth date, gender, credit card information, and email address (collectively, “personally identifiable information” or “personal information”). The personally identifiable information collected from our customers during the registration process is used to manage each customer’s account. We also seek such information to provide products and/or services that more closely reflect your preferences. In addition, we may use such personally identifiable information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze website usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our website’s content, layout, and services. 

### **Usage Information**

We automatically collect certain types of information when you use our Services. We may collect information about your device, including but not limited to the device type, operating system version, signal strength, whether it is on and how it is functioning, and device identifiers. We may also collect information related to your use of the device and the services you access through it, including but not limited to your call and data usage and history, your geolocation, the websites you visit, the applications purchased, downloaded, or used, and information about devices you tether to your device. We may link information we automatically collect from you with Personal Information, including information you provide to us and information we gather from other sources. We may use software to follow your use of our Services and other applications, including the use of cookies, web beacons, and other mechanisms, in addition to analysis of network and device information.  In accordance with federal law, we are required to obtain approval for use of customer proprietary network information, that relates to the quantity, technical configuration, type, destination, location, and amount of use of our service, and that is made available to us solely by virtue of the carrier-customer relationship, through methods described herein.

### **Personal Identification Number for Your Account**

To activate and manage your account and obtain access to certain services, we require you to provide a secret code (your “Service Passcode”). When using your account or providing your Service Passcode, you must provide accurate and complete information to Kroger Wireless. You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Service Passcode and are solely responsible for any activity conducted using your Service Passcode. You agree not to use the account, customer name, or Service Passcode of any other customer at any time unless that customer is under 18 and you are the parent or guardian of that customer. Prior to disclosing or releasing any personally identifiable, protectable information to you, we require entry of your Service Passcode for all phone or online requests and presentation of a valid photo ID for requests made in person.

### **Voluntary Surveys**

We may periodically conduct surveys of our customers and/or users of our websites (“survey participants”). We encourage you to participate in these voluntary surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third-party.

We take the information we receive from individuals responding to our surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other survey participants to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third-party affiliates.

**How Do We Use Your Information?**
-----------------------------------

As our customer, you have a right, and we—as your carrier—have a duty to protect the confidentiality of your customer proprietary network information.  However, unless you specifically decline by opting-out, we may use personally identifiable information to contact you and deliver information to you via your home phone, address, email, voice or text messages on your mobile phone if you are a Kroger Wireless customer. Unless you opt-out or otherwise object, we may also share personally identifiable information with certain third parties so that these third parties can share information with you about new products, services and promotions that we believe will interest you. By accepting this Privacy Policy or by purchasing or using our products or our jointly-branded products, you expressly agree to such usage and sharing of information. In addition, Kroger Wireless may use non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form for demographic marketing purposes, and may disclose this information to third parties, including advertisers.

If you are a Kroger Wireless customer, in certain special circumstances, we may contact you to deliver service-oriented messages, even if you have asked that we not contact you about special airtime events or promotions. These messages will be limited and only for this purpose.

We may use third-party providers to facilitate our services, and therefore, we may provide some of your personally identifiable information directly to them. In addition, we employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Some examples include fulfilling orders, providing mobile content, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. These service providers have access to personally identifiable information and may use it as needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for any other purpose, except that they may aggregate your personally identifiable information with similar information from other customers in a manner that does not potentially identify you.  Any third-party verification services are governed by those entities' separate privacy policies and not this policy.

We may share information with other third parties with your consent. For example, you may agree to our sharing your information with other third parties to hear about their products and services. Use of the information you agree to share will be subject to those third parties' separate privacy policies.

Kroger Wireless cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties, to enforce laws, such as protecting intellectual property rights and preventing fraud. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, to respond to lawful claims or legal process, to respond to emergencies, to protect the property of Kroger Wireless or the safety of its employees or others, to investigate fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is or may be illegal or expose you to liability.

It is possible that Kroger Wireless or its partners could be acquired or merged with another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that Kroger Wireless or its partners will share some or all of your personally identifiable information to continue to provide service. You will receive notice of such event (to the extent that it occurs), and we will request that the new combined entity follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy or notify you of any changes.

In accordance with federal law, we will maintain records of consumer consent to disclose or otherwise use customer proprietary network information for no less than one year.

We reserve the right to use, disclose, or permit access to your customer proprietary network information to protect our rights or property, or to protect users of our services and other carriers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, or subscription to, services.  We also reserve the right to use, disclose, or permit access to your customer proprietary network information without prior approval in our provisioning of inside wiring installation, maintenance, and repair services; and to conduct research on the health effects of CMRS. 

**What about Third-Party Applications and Services?**
-----------------------------------------------------

When using our Services, you may choose to use services and products offered by third parties, such as third-party applications. When you leave our network, you may also use mobile roaming services provided by third parties.

### **Your Use of Third-Party Applications** 

Your use of such services and applications may result in these third parties collecting your Personal Information and obtaining information from Kroger Wireless, including location information (when applicable). You may also choose to give your Personal Information directly to third parties when using our wireless services or devices. Except as noted below in the section Preinstalled Third Party Applications, the Personal Information you give to a third party will be subject to that third party's terms, conditions and policies—not this policy. You should always review a third party's privacy policy and terms of service before providing your Personal Information to them or using their services or products.

### **Third Party Compliance with Kroger Wireless Privacy Policy**    

If we use third parties, including but not limited to those noted above, and those third parties require the use of CPNI or other Personal Information, we require that such third parties take reasonable steps to protect the confidentiality of that information.

**How to Contact Us**
---------------------

If you would like to restrict the use or disclosure of your CPNI or other Personal Information for the marketing of certain products or services, you may contact us at 1-866-434-7796 from 9:00 am – 11:00 pm Eastern Time Monday through Saturday, and Sunday 10 am – 7 pm.  You may also e-mail us at cservice@iwirelesshome.com, or notify us in writing at Kroger Wireless, Attention: CPNI Officer, 1 Levee Way, Suite 3116, Newport, Kentucky, 41071 and provide your (1) Name, (2) Home Address, (3) Home telephone number (including area code), (4) Telephone number for your mobile phone (including area code), (5) Service billing address, and (6) Service account passcode.

**What Are Your Choices About Your Privacy?**
---------------------------------------------

If you are a Kroger Wireless customer, you may change the information that you have elected to share with us. You also have choices in the types of communications you wish to receive from us. When you activated your device, your notification preferences were set to receive notices about special offers, events and promotions from Kroger Wireless and special offers from our partners.

If you are a Kroger Wireless customer, to change your notification settings, or to change any of your personal information, you may do so by logging into the “My Account” page our website and updating your profile. Or, you may change your notification settings or any of your personal information by contacting customer care at 866-434-7796 (see also “How to Contact Us” section above).

**What About Cookies?**
-----------------------

“Cookies” are small files placed on your hard drive; each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser preferences allow it. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. (Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our websites and you may be required to re-enter your Service Passcode more frequently during a session. In addition, several companies not related to Kroger Wireless offer utilities designed to help you visit websites anonymously.

Cookies assist us in providing customized services and can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Kroger Wireless also uses cookies to remember you when you “sign in” to our websites, so that we can provide you with customized content, such as your balance, content targeted specifically for your phone, and other helpful services. Kroger Wireless cookies do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information. Kroger Wireless uses two kinds of cookies. Each time you log on to any of our websites, Kroger Wireless uses a “session cookie,” to help us to remember you until the earlier of approximately 30 minutes or the closing of your browser and to help make sure that you remain logged in to our website. Session cookies are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. We also use “persistent cookies,” which enable us to remember what is in your shopping cart for approximately two hours and to aggregate certain non-personally identifiable usage data in ways that help us to improve our services. Additionally, you may encounter cookies or other similar devices on our websites that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties, including third party websites to which we may link. Third party cookies or tools are governed by the privacy policies of the entities placing the ads and not by this Policy.

We use Google Analytics to help analyze how customers use our websites through the use of cookies. The information generation by the cookie about your use of our website (including your IP address) is transmitted to and stored by these analytical partners. This information is used for evaluating your use of our websites, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. These analytical partners may transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or to third parties that process information on its behalf. Neither partner will associate your IP address with any other data held regarding you.

**What Is Our Policy Toward Children?**
---------------------------------------

Kroger Wireless is concerned about the safety and privacy of children who use the Internet. Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent and may limit participation in certain services we provide to individuals over 13 years of age. At various places on our websites, we may request that customers provide a year of birth. If a child under the age of 13 responds to that request, we will direct him or her to have a parent or guardian call a live customer care agent at 866-434-7796, where a parent will be permitted to purchase a Kroger Wireless device, establish an account and activate on behalf of a child under 13. In these circumstances, activation can be made only by phone with a live customer care agent and the account must be in the parent’s name. A customer must be 18 to establish an account for a contract phone.

If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has or has attempted to provide us with personally identifiable information, we will use our best efforts to remove such information from our files. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has done this, he or she should contact the following customer care agent to remove this information:

Kroger Wireless Customer Resolutions  
1 Levee Way, Suite 3116  
Newport, KY 41071  
Telephone: 866-434-7796 (toll-free)  
Fax: (859) 261-6639 

**What Is Our Policy Regarding Location-Based Information?**
------------------------------------------------------------

Location-based information is information that indicates the location of your Kroger Wireless phone. When you turn on your mobile phone and use any of our location-based services, your device automatically communicates with our network and relays its current location. The accuracy of location-based services may be affected by circumstances beyond our control, including atmospheric, geographic location, or topographic conditions. We do not warrant or guarantee that location services will be available at any specific time or geographic location, or that service will be provided without interruption.

By using our location-based services, you consent to have us electronically collect, monitor, and track your physical location and the location of your handset. We collect and disclose your location information only to provide you with the location-based services you have requested, or in emergency situations as prescribed by law. If you allow other users to your handset, you are responsible for informing these users that their location information may be collected or disclosed. We will not provide your location information to third parties other than as prescribed without your consent.

If you are a Kroger Wireless customer and you wish to change your privacy options for the use of your location information, or if you no longer wish to use location-based services, please change the setting on your mobile phone by following the step-by-step instructions found in the User Guide specific to your handset. Changing your privacy options or terminating our location-based services will not affect the status of any other services you receive from us. Any information that is collected, monitored or tracked regarding your physical location or the location of your handset will not be retained longer than necessary to provide the location-based services you have selected.

**What About Other Information Collectors?**
--------------------------------------------

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information that we, or our partners, collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of your information. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**Is My Information Secure?**
-----------------------------

Kroger Wireless uses standard industry practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information and comply with all applicable federal regulations. I wireless treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company.

Unfortunately, perfect security does not exist on the Internet, and therefore, Kroger Wireless makes no representations or warranties regarding the sufficiency of our security measures. Kroger Wireless shall not be responsible for any damages that result from a lapse in compliance with this Privacy Policy because of a security breach, technical malfunction or similar problem. Always be careful and responsible regarding your personal information.

We are not responsible for, and cannot control, the use by others of any information, which you provide to them via our wireless services. Similarly, we cannot assume any responsibility for the content of any personal information or communication you receive from other customers through our wireless services.

**What Law Applies?**
---------------------

Our collection, use, access, disclosure and safeguarding of your personally identifiable information is subject to U.S. law. If you are a non-U.S. customer, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your personally identifiable information outside of your resident jurisdiction.

In addition, such personally identifiable information may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction. U.S. law may not provide the degree of protection for your information that is available in other countries. BY PROVIDING US WITH YOUR INFORMATION, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY, UNDERSTAND IT, AGREE TO ITS TERMS AND CONSENT TO THE TRANSFER OF SUCH INFORMATION OUTSIDE YOUR RESIDENT JURISDICTION. If you do not consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Services.

**Will This Privacy Policy Change?**
------------------------------------

Kroger Wireless may, from time to time, make changes to this Policy based on your comments and our need to accurately reflect our legal obligations and our data collection and disclosure practices. By continuing to use our Services or by calling Kroger Wireless at 866-434-7796, you agree to be bound by the latest version of this Policy, which may be viewed anytime by clicking on the Privacy Policy link at the foot of our websites.

**Want to Know More?**
----------------------

For questions or concerns about Kroger Wireless or our Services, please contact customer care by calling toll-free 1-866-434-7796 or by emailing care@krogerwireless.com. Calls to customer care may be monitored for quality assurance.

Find us in stores
-----------------

[

](https://www.kroger.com/)

Offers

Support

My Account

© 2024 Kroger Wireless LLC. All rights reserved.
